Guide to the Roy Radner Papers, 1951-2014 RL.11298
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Roy Radner papers
1951-2014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Radner, Roy, 1927-
RL.11298
36 Linear Feet
0.0028 Gigabytes
Roy Radner (1927- ) is an economic theorist and professor who has researched and taught at University of California at Berkeley, the Cowles Commission, AT&T Bell Lab, and New York University. His archival collection includes his published writings, drafts, collaborations, correspondence, and teaching materials spanning the length of his career.
Biographical / Historical
Roy Radner was Born in Chicago on June 29th 1927 and is currently the Leonard N. Stern Professor of Business at New York University. He studied mathematics from 1945 to 1956 at the University of Chicago. There, he obtained a Ph.D. in mathematical statistics entitled Team Decision Functions (1956) under the supervision of Leonard Savage. He was also a researcher at the Cowles Commission from 1951 to 1957, before moving to the University of California Berkeley (1957-1969), making a quick passage at Harvard (1977-1979), and then spending some years at AT&T Bell Lab (1979-1995) that overlapped with its beginning at New York University (1983-). Throughout these years, he worked as a consultant for various private and public entities.
He is probably most well-known among scholars for three contributions. The first one on the theory of "Team", especially with Jacob Marschak, which culminated in the 1972 publication of the book Economic Theory of Team. The second one is on growth theory with his 1961 contribution to the so-called "Turnpike Theorems". The third one is on general equilibrium theory with time and uncertainty, where he introduced a notion of equilibrium involving rational expectations in the early 1970s, today (meaning 2016) known as a "Radner Equilibrium" in financial economics. More generally, Radner made key contributions on the economics of information and on bounded rationality in economics. He is married to economist Charlotte Kuh, and has collaborated with her on some papers.
Access Restrictions
Correspondence Series is closed until 2050 due to prolific personnel and tenure review files and recommendations.
Provenance
The Roy Radner Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2015.
Collection Overview
The Roy Radner Papers contain 6 series. The series "Writings" (1951-2013) includes Radner's published and unpublished papers, with various materials related to them (e.g., correspondence with editors and colleagues, multiple drafts with hand-written notes, hand-written sheets of mathematical developments etc.). The series "Correspondence" (1954-2014) includes his correspondence sorted by individuals' names. Files include correspondence with and about, or only about, the individual named on a given file. There is also a set of personal files. Due to the large number of recommendation letters and other personnel-related content of the Correspondence series, this portion of the collection is restricted until 2050. The series "Teaching" (1967-2012) contains materials related to his teaching activity (e.g., syllabus, reading lists and packets, exercises with solutions). The bulk of it is largely from the Stern School (New York University) from the late 1990s to the early 2010s. The series "Research Activities" (1962-2014) includes materials about activities such as seminars, workshops, study groups and the like. Finally, the series "Writings by Others" (1954-2006) contains materials written by other researchers, with or (in most cases) without notes from Radner. There are no specific connections among the series to be noted, except the fact that, by virtue of their thematic organizations, one can find academic and administrative letters in all the series, i.e., not only in "Correspondence."
Collection contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Arrangement
The collection arrived from Roy Radner fairly well divided into six groups: "Published Papers" (6 boxes), "Notes on Published Papers" (2 boxes), "Notes on Research" (4 boxes), "Correspondence" (7 boxes), "Miscellaneous Files/Papers" (1 box) and "Teaching Notes" (5 boxes). "Correspondence" remained practically untouched, a very small number of letters from the other files have been refiled here. "Teaching Notes" has been renamed "Teaching", and re-organized alphabetically. For the same reason, the remaining of the four series that has not been refiled elsewhere has been collapsed into three new series: "Writings," "Research Activities," and "Writings by Others". Duplicates and student grades/coursework have been removed from the collection. Accordingly, it should be noted that the series "Research Activities" partly overlaps with "Teaching" in the sense that most workshops run by Radner could be attended by students, and the latter could be graded on a paper about the contents of these workshops.
Game theory -- Research; Economics -- Mathematical models; Environmental economics; Economic history; Equilibrium (Economics); Turnpike theory (Economics); Hurwicz, Leonid; Arrow, Kenneth J. (Kenneth Joseph), 1921-2017; Hahn, Frank; Dutta, Prajit K.; Majumdar, Mukul, 1944-; Marschak, Jacob, 1898-1977; Debreu, Gerard; Linhart, Peter B.; Cowles Commission for Research in Economics; University of Chicago. Dept. of Economics; Leonard N. Stern School of Business
- Writings, 1951-2013; 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes Radner's published and unpublished papers from 1951 until 2013, with various materials related to them. Such materials can include: correspondence with editors and colleagues, multiple drafts with hand-written notes, hand-written sheets of mathematical developments, numerical sheets of simulation or experimental data, others' papers (not always annoted), transparencies and other oral presentation-related materials, and articles cut from newspapers and magazines. Most of the papers are academic; those that are related to his consulting activities have typically then served as the basis for subsequent academic publications.
  - Allocation of Resources in a Team, 1971 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - The Allocation of Value for Jointly Produced Services, 1993-1995; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - The Application of Linear Programming to Decision Problems, 1957-1958 and undated (Box 1)
  - Approximate Purification of Mixed Strategies, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Arrow Lectures, 1993-1996; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Balanced Stochastic Growth at the Maximum Rate, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Behavior and Efficiency in the Sealed-Bid Mechanism, 1985-1990 and undated; 6 folders (Box 1)
  - A Behavioral Model of Cost Redution, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - Behavioral Models of Stochastic Control, 1986 (Box 1)
  - The Best is the Enemy of the Good, 1979-2001 (Box 1)
  - BMD, Models of Deterrence, Undated (Box 1)
  - Bounded Rationality, Indeterminacy, and the Managerial Theory of the Firm, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Can Bounded Rationality Resolve the Prisoners' Dilemma, 1978-1986; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Capital Growth in a Global Warming Model, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Collusive Behavior in NonCooperative Epsilon-Equilibria of Oligopolies with Long but Finite Lives, 1978-1988 (Box 1)
  - Competitive Equilibrium Under Uncertainty, 1965-2000 (Box 1)
  - Competitive Pricing Strategies, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Communication in Networks, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Consistent Decision Functions and Bayes Solutions, 1952-1953 (Box 1)
  - Consumer Benefit from Federal Preemption of Nationalwide Caller ID, 1993-1994 and undated (Box 1)
  - Costly and Bounded Rationality in Individual and Team Decision-Making, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Decentralization and Incentives, 1985-1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Decision and Organization, 1972-2002 and undated (Box 1)
    Contains correspondence between V. Smith, L. Hurwicz, L. Savage
  - Decision Rules Based on Failure-Restoration Processes, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Demand and Supply in U.S. Higher Education, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Deregulation of Long-Distance Telecommunications, 1982-1984 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - The Design Performance of Sharing Rules for a Partnership in Continuous Time, 1988-1996; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Designing a Discrete Product Line in a Monopoly, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Detecting a Paramter Change in an IID Process, 1996 and undated (Box 2)
  - Discussion of M. Bray, Convergence to Rational Expectations Equilibrium, 1981-1983 (Box 2)
  - Discussion of K. John and J. Ronen, "The temporal Evolution of Profit Measures…", 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Does Decentralization Promote Wasteful Conflict, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Dollar Auction - Minimax Regret Strategies, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Games in Organization Theory, 1989-1998; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Market Evolution, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Pricing of Network Goods with Boundedly Rational Consumers, 2003-2013; 10 folders (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Programming, 1974-1976 and undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Programming of Economic Growth, 1963-1967; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Economic Planning Under Uncertainty: Recent Theoretical Developments, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Economic Survival, 1995-1998 and undated; 11 folders (Box 2)
  - Economic Theory of Teams, 1958-1973 (Box 3)
  - The Economic Value of Information, undated (Box 3)
  - Effects of Increasing the Subscriber Line Charge on Total Surplus and on GNP, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - The Effect on Prices and Outputs of Productivity Growth in a Leontief Input-Output Model with one Primary Resource, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Efficiency in Partnership when the Joint Output is Uncertain, 1986-1995; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Efficiency Prices for Infinite Horizon Production Programs, 1966-1968 and undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Encyclopedic Handbook of the Mathematical Economic Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Equilibre des marches a terme et au comptant en cas d'incertitude, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Equilibria of the Sealed-Bid Mechanism for Bargaining with Incomplete Information, 1986-1989 (Box 3)
  - Equilibrium of Spot and Futures Markets Under Uncertainty, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Equilibrium Under Uncertainty, 1977-1982 (Box 3)
  - The Evaluation of Information in Organizations, 1961 (Box 3)
  - An Example of a Repeated Partnership Game with Discounting and with Uniformity Equilibria, 1983-1986; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Existence of an Optimal Control for the Model of Section 3, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Existence of Equilibrium of Plans, Prices, and Prices Expectations in a Sequence of Markets, Part I and II, 1970-2007 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Allocation and Revealed Equity, 1973-1977; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Faculty-Student Ratios in U.S. Higher Education, 1976 (Box 3)
  - The Firm as a Team - Abstract, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Friends and Family and Related Pricing Strategies, 1991-1994 (Box 3)
  - A Game Theoretic Approach to Global Warming, 1999-2006; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Hierarchy: The Economics of Managing, 1989-2001 and undated; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - A Hitting-Probability Inequality for Strict Submartingales, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Information Overload, 1990 and undated (Box 3)
  - Information Pooling and Decentralized Decision-Making, 1984-1986 (Box 3)
  - Information Processing and Returns to Scale in Statistical Decision Problems, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Information Processing in Firms Return to Scale, 1991-1994 (Box 3)
  - Informational Externalities and the Scope of Efficient Dominant Strategy Mechanisms, 1985-1988 (Box 3)
  - Information, Incentives, and Economic Mechanisms, 1983-1989 (Box 4)
  - Information: Value, Cost, and Return to Scale, 1992 and undated (Box 4)
  - The Internal Economy of Large Firms, 1985-2003 (Box 4)
  - International Encyclopedia of Social and Behavioral Sciences: Costly and Bounded Rationality, 2012 (Box 4)
  - Intertemporal General Equilibrium, 1988-1990 (Box 4)
  - IT Labor Market Dynamics, 1999-2000 and undated; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Jacob Marschak, 1984-1991 (Box 4)
  - Jacob Marschak and the Theory of Decision and Organization, Undated (Box 4)
  - Joint Exploitation of a Productive Asset: A Game-Theoretic Approach, 1987-1992 (Box 4)
  - Learning about the Learning Curve, 1993-1998; 4 folders (Box 4)
  - Limit Distributions of Failure Time for Series-Parallel System, 1958-1959; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Linear Models of Economic Survival Under Production Uncertainty, 1987-1991 (Box 4)
  - The Linear Team: An Example of Linear Programming Under Uncertainty, 1954-1956 (Box 4)
  - Market Adjustment in Disequilibrium with Random Disturbances, 1975-2008 (Box 4)
  - Market Equilibrium and Uncertainty: Concepts and Problems, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Market Power in the Interexchange Market, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Markets under Uncertainty, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Mathematical Specification of Goals for Decision Problems, 1964 and undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Mathematicians in Academia: 1975-2000, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Minimax Estimation for Linear Regressions, 1955-1959; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Minimax Regret Strategies for Barganing over several Variables, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - A Model of Defense-Protected Build-Down, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Un modele de choix binaires stochastique, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Monitoring Cooperative Agreements between Principals and Agents, 1979-1989 (Box 4)
  - Monopolists and Viscuous Demand, 1997-2003; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Moral Hazard, 1989-1994; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - National Needs and the Declining Supply of Young Scientists, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Natural Resource Damage Assessments under the Oil Pollution Act of 1990, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Neo-Schumpeterian and Other Theories of the Firm: A Comment and Personal Retrospective, 2004-2006; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - The New Palgrave - General, 1983-1988 (Box 5)
  - The New Palgrave - Jacob Marschak, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - New Palgrave - Teams, 1987 (Box 5)
  - New Palgrave - Uncertainty and General Equilibrium, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - The New Palgrave 2nd Edition - General, 2006 (Box 5)
  - The New Palgrave 2nd Edition - Teams, 2006 and undated (Box 5)
  - The New Palgrave 2nd Edition - Uncertainty and General Equilibrium, 1986-2007; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - A nonconcavity in the Value of Information, 1975-1998; 4 folders (Box 5)
  - A Note on Exact Purification, 1981-1983 and undated (Box 5)
  - Note on Generalized Convex Functions and the Decision Problem, 1951 and undated (Box 5)
  - A Note on Maximal Points of Convex Sets, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Note on Some Proposed Decision Criteria, 1952-1954 (Box 5)
  - A Note on the Ruin of an Indebted Investor, 1989 (Box 5)
  - A Note on the Theory of Cost-Benefit Analysis in the Small, 1972-1993; 4 folders (Box 5)
  - A Note on Unanimity of Stockholders' Preferences among Alternative Production Plans: A Reformulation of Ekern-Wilson Model, 1973-2007 (Box 5)
  - Notes on a Diffusion Model of Economic Survival under Uncertainty, 1986-1989 and undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Notes on Division of Labor in the University of the Future, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Notes on Duality in Linear Programming, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Notes on Fairness within a Corporation, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Notes on Groves Mechanisms in Transfer Pricing, 1984 and undated (Box 5)
  - Notes on the Groves/Loet Mechanism, 1981 and undated (Box 5)
  - Notes on Multi-Stage R, 1981-2001 (Box 5)
  - Notes on Profit Centers, 1983 and undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Notes on R, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Notes on Transfer Pricing, Cost Allocation, and Cooperation Among Business Units and Support Divisions, 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Notes on the Expected Discounted Time to Failure, 1986 and undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Notes on the Formal Model of Input-Output Analysis, 1972-1979 (Box 5)
  - Notes on the Theory of Economic Planning, 1963 (Box 5)
  - On the Allocation of Effort, 1974-1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Core of a Cartel, 1976-2001 (Box 6)
  - On the Market for Data-Networking Products, 1989-1990 and undated (Box 6)
  - On Optimal Communication Rules for Certain Types of Teams, 1953 (Box 6)
  - On the Optimal Schedule for Introducing a New Technology, 1990-1999 and undated; 5 folders (Box 6)
  - Opportunistic Replacement of a Single Part in the Presence of Several Monitored Parts, 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Optimal Growth in a Linear-Logarithmic Economy, 1962-1966; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Optimal Principal Agent Contracts for a Class of Incentive Schemes: A Characterization the Rate of Approach to Efficiency, 1991-1994; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Optimal Replacement and Inspection of Stochastically Failing Equipment, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Optimal Stationary Consumption with Stochastic Production and Resources, 1972-1989 (Box 6)
  - Optimal Steady-State Behavior of an Economy with Stochastic Production and Resources, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Organization of Decentralized Information Processing, 1989-2003; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - The Organization of Decision Problems, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Paths of Economic Growth that are Optimal with Regard to Final States: Two 'Turnpike Theorem', 1960-2008 (Box 6)
  - Petty Corruption: A Game-Theoretic Approach, 2008-2007 (Box 6)
  - Perspectives on Deterrence, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Politiques optimales d'entretien et de remplacement dans les systemes a plusieurs elements, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Population Growth and Technological Change in a Global Warming Model, 2004-2006; 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Preserving a Lost Generation: Policies to Assure a Steady Flow of Young Scholars Until the Year 2000, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Price Caps, 1987-1992; 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Principal-Agent Games in Continuous Time, 1987-1998 (Box 7)
  - Private Information and Pure-Strategy Equilibria, 1980-1982 (Box 7)
  - Problems in the Theory of Markets under Uncertainty, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - A Profit-Center Game with Incomplete Information, 1994-1999; 5 folders (Box 7)
  - Profit Centers, Transfer Prices and the Core of the Game, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Profit Maximization and the Market Selection Hypothesis, 1996-1998; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Profit Maximization with Bankruptcy and Variable Scale, 1996-1997; 3 folders (Box 7)
  - The Quadratic Team. I, 1954 (Box 7)
  - R, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Radner on Marschak, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Rational Expectations Equilibrium: Generic…, 1976-1980 (Box 7)
  - Rational Expectations in Micro-Economic Models: An Overview, 1981-1982 (Box 7)
  - Rational Selection of a Decision Function in an Observable Situation, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Real-Time Decentralized Information Processing and Returns to Scale, 1995-2000; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Relaxed Regulation of AT, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Repeated Games, 1978-1980 and undated (Box 8)
  - Repeated Moral Hazard with Low Discount Rates, 1982-1985 and undated; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Repeated Partnership Games with Imperfect Monitoring and No Discounting, 1981-1986 and undated; 3 folders (Box 8)
    File 3 possibly belong to files "An Example of a Repeated Partnership Game with Discounting and with Uniformity Equilibria"
  - A Repeated Principal-Agent Game with Discounting, 1981-1985 (Box 8)
  - Risk vs. Profit-Potential; A Model for Corporate Strategy, 1994-1996 (Box 8)
  - Robert W. Rosenthal, 2003-2004 (Box 8)
  - Robustness of a Class of Bargaining Mechanisms, 1990-1993 (Box 8)
  - Robustness of the Sealed-Bid Bargaining Mechanism: Experiment Theory, 1991-1992 and undated (Box 8)
  - The Role of Private Information in Markets and Other Organizations, 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Satisficing, 1975-2001 (Box 8)
  - The Sealed-Bid Mechanism: An Experimental Study, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 8)
    File 2 also belong with "Equilibria of the Sealed-Bid Mechanism for Bargaining with Incomplete Information"
  - Self-Enforcing Climate-Change Treaties, 2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - A Sequential Mechanism for Direct Price Regulation, 1983-1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - A Sequential Principal-Agent Approach to Regulation, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Shadow Prices for Infinite Growth Programs: The Functional Analysis Approach, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - A Simple Model of Aggregate IT Labor Dynamics, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Stationary Optimal Policies with Discounting…, 1980-1989 (Box 9)
  - Stochastic Coombs Model, 1961 (Box 9)
  - A Stochastic Decentralized Allocation Process, 1960-1975 and undated; 9 folders (Box 9)
  - Some Stochastic Models of Administrative Allocation, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Stochastic Stability of Market Adjustment in Disequilibrium, 1975-1979 (Box 9)
  - A Strategic Analysis of Global Warming, 2001-2007; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Strategic Analysis of Petty Corruption, 2001-2009 and undated; 14 folders (Box 9)
  - Structural and Operational Communication Problems in Team, 1953 (Box 9)
  - Survival under Production Uncertainty, 1981-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
    File 2 may go with the file "Linear Models of Economic Survival Under Production Uncertainty"
  - Symposium on Bargaining, 1986-1992; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Team Decision Functions, 1954-1956 (Box 9)
    Radner's Ph.D. thesis
  - Team Decision Problems, 1962 and undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Technical Innovation and Regulatory Change, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Technical Notes on the Gamblers Ruin Problem in Continuous Time, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Testing Two Precise Hypotheses about the Mean of a Gaussian Vector, 1989 and undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - A Theory of the Movement and Solution of Problems within an Organization, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Transfer Payments and the Core of a Profit-Center Game, 1984-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Use of a Bayesian Techniques for Predicting Spare-Parts Demand, 1960; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - The Use of Mathematics in Economics (V.S. Nemchinov, ed.) - A Book Review, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Viscuous Demand, 1992-2003 and undated; 23 folders (Box 10)
  - Ways of Doing Business Overseas, 1985; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Collections of Data Related to The Softwar Sector, 1985-1987 and undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Documents on "Bureaucracy", 1970-1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 10)
    Original file name: "Bureaucracy"
  - Unidentified Files on Growth, 1961-1963 and undated; 7 folders (Box 10)
    Original files names: "Turnpike - Notes", "Competitive Equilibrium, Infinite No. of Generations, Diamond Model", "Proportional Growth", "Math. Prog of Growth", "Decomposition", "Decomposition Current Problems", "Notes on Growth with Trade"
  - Unidentified Hand-Written Notes, Undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Hand-Written Notes Related to AT, 1987-1988 and undated (Box 10)
    Original file name: "Software Productivity"
  - Unidentified Hand-Written Notes Related to Drew Fudenberg and Jean Tirole's "Sequential Bargaining with Incomplete Information" (1983), Undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Mathematical Developments and Computations, Undated (Box 10)
    Original file name: "Efficient Trees"
  - Unidentified Notes on Compact Subsets and Infinite Games, Undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Notes on Estimation with Piece-Wise Linear Function, Undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Notes on Labor Statistics, Undated (Box 10)
    Original file name: "ML Notes for New Tables"
  - Unidentified Notes on Searching for a Trade, Undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Notes on Stopping Rules, Undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Paper with Linhart, 1984 and undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Presentation (1), Undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Presentation (2), 1992 and undated (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Writings on "The Manager-Company Game", 1984 and undated (Box 10)
- Correspondence, 1959-2014; 2